Hello.
こんにちは
She's such a cute girl.
すんごい可愛い子だね
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとうございます
What's your name?
名前何て言うんですか?
This is Koyuki.
小雪です
Koyuki-chan.
小雪ちゃん
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
He looks like a celebrity.
芸能人みたいなルックスしてるよ
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
You'll be extremely popular, right?
めちゃくちゃモテるでしょ
I'm extremely unpopular.
めちゃくちゃモテないです
Really?
本当に?
If you see a cute girl like this, everyone will turn their heads.
こんな可愛い子いたら、 みんな振り向いちゃうよ
How old is this child now?
こういう子ちゃん今何歳?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18 years old.
18歳
What are you playing at 18 years old?
18歳今何して遊んでるの?
I'm a student.
学生です
So, are you busy with school?
じゃあ学校に忙しいのかな?
that's right.
そうです
So what do you do on your day off?
じゃあお休みの日何やってんの?
I work part-time on my days off.
お休みの日はバイトしてます
What part-time job do you do?
何のバイトやってるの?
It's family.
ファミリスです
Family?
フ ァミリス?
is.
です
Are you going to bring the food?
お料理運んだりしちゃうの?
that's right.
そうです
That's right.
そうなんだ
You're seriously trying your best.
真面目に頑張ってんだね
You've never taken a photo like this before, have you?
こんな撮影したことないでしょ?
No.
ないです
I'm a student and a family worker.
学生やってファミリス働いてるんだね
I get the impression that a very serious girl has come.
すごい真面目な子が来たなっていう印象だけど
Is school quite busy?
学校は結構忙しいの?
I'm busy.
忙しいです
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今彼氏はいる?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
Why aren't you there?
なんでいないの?
Because you can't.
できないからです
What kind of cancer do you want?
欲しいがんぼは?
Limited time only.
期間限定
From class 2 mast.
クラス2マストから
I want it now.
今 欲しいですね
Is that so?
そう か
Do you get lonely?
寂しくなっちゃう?
yes.
そう
Don't you usually feel lonely?
普段は寂しくなんない?
I don't feel lonely.
寂しくなんないです
yes?
そう?
It doesn't really feel like a love story.
あんまり恋愛対策って感じじゃないんだ
What kind of person do you like?
どういう人が好きなの?
Um...
えっと...
A slightly unusual person.
ちょっと普通じゃない人
Someone who is not normal?
普通じゃない人?
Does that mean you like people who are different?
変わってる人がいいってこと?
that's right.
そうです
Why do you like strange people?
なんで変わってる人が好きなの?
Isn't that rare?
珍しくない?
It's just kind of boring.
なんか普通つまんない
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Even though you look so clean.
こんな清素な見た目してるのに
It's an interesting mentality.
面白いメンタルなの
I'm not a fan of handsome Johnny's.
イケメンのジョニーズが好きな奥じゃないんだ
Who do you look like?
見た目だと誰?
It looks...
見た目は...
Kubozuka-kun.
久保塚くん
Kubozuka.
久保塚ね
It hasn't changed.
変わってんね
surely.
確かに
But it's cool.
でもかっこいいよね
Are you okay with yourself?
自分のこといいですか?
Which do you think it is now?
今どっちだと思う?
I don't know yet.
まだ分かんないです
Don't you understand?
分かんないか
How many people have experience?
経験率何人?
Um...
えっと...
About 3 or 4 people.
3、4人くらい
Ah, 3 or 4 people.
あ、 3、4人か
Oh, what about your boyfriend?
え、彼氏は?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
How many boyfriends have you had so far?
今まで何人、彼氏は?
I have two boyfriends.
彼氏は2人
So maybe once or twice with someone who isn't your boyfriend?
じゃあ彼氏じゃない人とも 1回か2回くらい?
that's right.
そうです
I've had sex before.
エッチしたことあるんだ
Why did you have sex with him even though he wasn't your boyfriend?
なんでそれは彼氏じゃないのに エッチしちゃったの?
Hmm.
うーん
Have you ever had sex?
エッチしたこと?
keep company...
付き合う...
I think it's important to have a relationship.
付き合うのに 大事なものかなと
I see.
なるほどね
Before we started dating.
付き合う前にね
Do you like doing naughty things?
エッチなことすんのは好きなの?
yes.
はい
I like it.
好きなんだ
Have you ever had sex with yourself?
自分のことエッチしたことある?
I don't know.
わかんないです
Ah, I said it earlier.
あ、さっき言ったね
Yeah.
うん
Until now, it was a strange and exciting episode.
今まででさ、 なんか変わったエッチっていうか 興奮したエピソ
Is there such a thing as a code?
ード とかある?
And I made her my friend's sex friend.
と、友達のセフレとした
Friend's sex friend?
友達のセフレ?
What is the situation?
どういう状況?
When I went home, he was there.
なんか、おうち行ったら いたんで
Was it a man?
男の人だったの?
yes.
そう
Why did you decide to have sex with it?
なんでそれ、エッチすることになったの?
Because he was my type.
タイプだったから
Did you invite me?
誘ったの?
From myself.
自分から
yes.
そう
He's a bad boy.
悪い子だね
I do things like that.
そんなこともしちゃうんだ
I can't imagine it from this face.
この顔からは想像できない
Are you nervous today?
今日緊張してる?
I am doing.
してます
Are you doing it?
してるか
This is not how it was taken.
こうやって取られたもんないもんね
yes.
はい
Well then, Koike-chan.
じゃあ、小池ちゃん
yes.
はい
Could you please stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらえる?
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Has anyone ever told you that you look alike?
誰か似てるって言われたことある?
And Erika-chan from Nogizaka.
と、乃木坂の 行くたえりかちゃん
I kind of understand.
ちょっと分かる
Have them turn around.
後ろ向いてもらう
Look at me with your face.
顔でこっち見て
Your style is amazing.
スタイルすごいね
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
It's 63.
63です
63?
I'm so excited.
ドキドキしちゃうね
A girl you like with your own body?
自分の体で好きな子?
Sakotsu?
サコツ?
Do you like sakotsu?
サコツ好きなの?
She's smiling and cute.
ニコニコして可愛いな
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Why do you like Sakotsu?
なんでサコツが好きなの?
Somehow.
なんとなく
Do you like Sakotsu for some reason?
なんとなくサコツ好きなの?
I see.
そうか
Kuru-chan, come next to me.
くるちゃん、隣に来て
Hello.
こんにちは
Which kind of pervert?
どこの変態感?
Good, I think it's good.
いい、いいと思う
Do you think it's good?
いいと思う?
I see.
そっか
Kuru-chan, apparently it's me, Nogi-chan.
くるちゃん、どうやら逆に俺、乃木ちゃん
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いっすね
It has a sense of transparency.
透明感があって
You look like an idol, right?
アイドルみたいでしょ?
It's definitely worth going to.
確かに行くたえりかっぽいわ
Well then, Kuru-chan.
じゃあ、くるちゃん
Can you stretch my shirt?
シャツ伸ばしてもらえる?
Is it okay?
いいっすか?
Kuru-chan, Rion, etc.
くるちゃん、リオンとか
Well then, please excuse me for a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと失礼します
Is this also good?
こっちもいい?
yes.
はい
You have very beautiful breasts.
めっちゃ綺麗なおっぱいしてるね
copper?
どう?
What about breasts?
おっぱいたら?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
By yourself?
自分で?
You have an amazing body.
すげー色い体してるね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you want me to touch your butt?
お尻、プリってつけ出してもらう?
Get your ass out.
お尻、つけ出して
Bring it out.
つけ出す
My face fell.
顔がひっくりして
Call me Puri.
プリってつけ出して
Kuru-chan, come here.
くるちゃん、こっちおいで
My skin is sour.
肌、渋いっすね
This is great, Kuru-chan.
最高でしょ、くるちゃん、これ
What do you want to do?
どうしたい?
I just licked it all over my body.
ちょっと、体中いっぱい舐め回したんですけど
Can I have a drink?
飲みましていい?
Yeah.
うん
Have you been touched by a man for the first time in a while?
久しぶりの男の人に触られた?
You have a very naughty body.
すんごいエッチな体してるね
I'm standing up so tall.
すげーチクブ立ってる
I did get breasts though.
おっぱいもらえてたもんだけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'm feeling a bit nervous.
なんかチクビ立ってるよ
Yeah.
うん
Just a little touch.
ちょっと触られただけ
Why are you standing?
なんで立ってんの?
why?
なんで?
Because it's human.
人間だから
Does it feel good?
気持ちよだっちゃう?
Do you like being kind?
優しいの好き?
Yeah.
うん
As expected, be kind.
やっぱり優しく
Isn't there such a thing?
そんなもんない?
You've never been licked by someone under your arm, have you?
脇の人舐められたことないでしょ?
yes.
はい
Can I lick your armpits too?
脇も舐めていい?
Yeah.
うん
It's all my first experience.
初体験ばっかりだね
It's so easy, isn't it?
すんびんびんなんでしょ
Kuru-chan, what do you think of the 18-year-old chikubi?
くるちゃん、18歳のチクビどう?
It's really delicious.
めっちゃ美味しいです
Isn't her face cute when her breasts are licked?
おっぱい舐められてる顔可愛いでしょ?
I've made it look like this.
こんなピンピンにしちゃってる
My amazingly delicious-looking breasts are licked
すんげぇ美味しそうなおっぱい舐められて
Ru.
る
So, could you please take off those pants?
じゃあ そのパンツ脱いでもらえる?
yes.
はい
Can you open it slowly?
ゆっくり開いてもらえる?
I'm more confused.
もっと迷いで
That's an amazing little mango.
すんげぇちっちゃいマンゴーだね
That's amazing, isn't it?
すんげぇワッピンか
I can smell it.
匂い嗅いだね
But this mango is cute.
でも可愛いこのマンゴー
Can you lick me?
舐められる?
It smells great.
えらい匂いが
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいい?
Kuru-chan while opening a mango.
くるちゃんマンゴー開きながら
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Are you being licked by a mango?
マンゴー舐められてる?
It's small and amazing.
ちっちゃいすごい
Isn't it tough?
きついんじゃない?
this.
これ
It's very narrow, isn't it?
めちゃくちゃ狭いでしょ?
Ah, you got a nice finger in there.
あ、いい指入っちゃったね
It's amazing how the roots have gone in.
すごい根元も入っちゃったじゃん
I'm making a kuribinbin.
くりびんびんにしてる
How do you feel?
あんな気持ち?
Yeah.
うん
Brain bag is getting wet?
脳袋ちゃん濡れてきた?
A great manjurt is made.
すんごいマンジュルタができてる
Yo.
よ
This is Yuki-chan.
こ ゆきちゃん
yes.
はい
What is this?
これなんだ?
This is dick.
これ、ちんちん
Chin Chin?
ちんちん?
See you for the first time in a while?
久しぶり見る?
Yeah.
うん
It's getting hard.
固くなってる
Is it already hard?
もう固くなってる?
Who is to blame?
誰のせい?
Koyuki-chan is so cute that his penis is standing up.
こゆきちゃん可愛いからちんこ立っちゃったって
I agree.
そうだね
happy?
嬉しい?
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いする?
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
Kuru-chan, why is this dick?
くるちゃんこのちんこどうして?
I want you to feel good.
気持ちよくしてほしい
cute.
可愛い
Have you ever had a face like this?
こんな顔当てられたことある?
do not have.
ない
yes.
はい
You like big dicks, right?
でっかいちんちん好きでしょ?
Everything about Kuru-chan is so cute
全部くるちゃん可愛くてる
Yo.
よ
You have a really cute face.
す んごい可愛い顔してんじゃん
Will you make me feel good with that pero?
そのペロでいっぱい気持ちよくしてくれる?
Yeah.
うん
Is the big girl delicious?
でっかいちゃんおいしい?
Yeah.
うん
How cute is it?
どこまで可愛いてる?
Is it really painful?
すごく苦しいの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm so happy that I just happened to catch it.
たまたまにつくくらいはもう一気にほくまいちゃうと
Faster.
もっと早く
copper?
どう?
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
He talks so much.
すげえちんちんこ喋るじゃん
Spit on this.
これでつばだらして
I talked about people.
人を喋った
Put it all in your mouth.
全部口に入れて
I want a hard penis.
かたいちんちんほしい
Yeah.
うん
I want you to spit on me.
つばつけてほしい
I want you to say that my dick is delicious.
ちんちんおいしいですって言ってほしい
It's so delicious.
ちんちんおいしいです
Kuru-chan's penis is plump.
くるちゃんちんこパンパンだよ
It's delicious.
おいしいね
Kuru-chan Chin-chan.
くるちゃんちんちゃん
Shall I get wet in bed?
ベッドでじめるか?
Yuki-chan, come here.
こ ゆきちゃんこっち来て
Koyuki-chan.
こゆきちゃん
yes.
はい
Well, I'll recommend it now.
じゃあ今からすめるからさ
Can I have you sleep there?
そこ寝てもらっていい?
You like it from top to bottom, right?
上から下まで好きでしょ
It really makes my mouth stand up.
ほんとすめちくび立っちゃうね
Delicious Kuru-chan.
おいしいくるちゃん
Is it better to use this?
これ使ったほうがある?
Do you have this?
これある?
It's a phone.
電話だよ
Yeah.
うん
Can I use this to make you feel better?
これ使ってくる気持ちよくしていい?
Yeah.
うん
Is your pussy twitching?
まんこひくひくしてる?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
Why don't you just go to sleep?
勝手に一応寝ない?
If I sleep, if I sleep.
寝たら寝たら
Should I sleep?
寝ちゃったほうがいい?
Yeah.
うん
Should I sleep again?
もう 一回寝たほうがいい?
strange.
おかしい
Have you fallen asleep yet?
まだ寝ちゃったの?
Yeah.
うん
You have a very sexy face.
すごいエロい顔してるよ
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいい?
If you sleep
寝すれば
Amazing, my pussy is twitching.
すごい おまんこひくひくしてるよ
Can I use one on the plate?
もっとさ、皿にいっちなやつ使っていい?
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever put this much in?
こんなに入れたことある?
do not have.
ない
do not have?
ない?
Come in, this little pussy.
入るから、このちっちゃいまんこひ
Ku hikiku.
く ひく
This is included.
これ入ってる
I know there's a thick one in there.
わかる太いの入ってる
copper?
どう?
once again.
もう一度
I want you to sleep well.
ゆっくり寝てほしい
Should I go back to sleep?
もう一回寝たほうがいい?
A little pussy jerking
ちょっと四つんまんこひく
Draw.
ひ く
More butt palms.
もっとお尻つきやし
Look at my face.
顔こっち見て
Stand up on your knees.
膝ちゃんと立てて
Let go.
離して
So I'll confirm this too.
じゃあこれも肯定する
This time, from Kuru-chan's Earth.
今度、くるちゃんの地球からさ
Can you keep attacking me?
どんどん攻めてってもらえる?
Do you like licking?
なめるの好き?
Yeah.
うん
Keep doing it.
どんどんして
Make your dick feel good.
いっぱいちんちん気持ちよくして
delicious?
おいしい?
Yeah.
うん
Spit on it and squeeze it.
つばたらし、しこしこして
Down, wobbling.
下、ふらふら
The two at the back are licking it.
後ろ二人でなめやくして
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
Become velvety.
ベロベロになって
Lately, I've been popping it.
最近、ぽぺろぺろ
More twigs.
もっとちぽちぽっと
What do you want to do, Kuru-chan?
くるちゃんどうしたい?
Hey, can you hold the penis yourself and put it in there?
てか、ちんちん自分で持って、ちんちん入れてくれる?
More and more penis.
どんどんちんちん
How about Kuru-chan?
くるちゃんどう?
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
It's so tight, pussy.
きついでしょ、おまんこ
It's hitting me, you know.
ぶっ刺さってるよ、ほら
Does your hard penis feel good?
かたいちんも気持ちいい?
Wow, mangel is spilling out.
すげえマンジェルこぼれてるよ
I got a lot of pussy.
いっぱいおまんこついてもらえた
I was shown a lot of locations.
いっぱいロケを見せてもらえた
This pussy is so tight, Kuru-chan.
きついね、くるちゃん、このまんこ
It's really tight.
めっちゃきつい
Look at where my penis is stuck.
ちんちん刺さってるとこ見てほら
Look at where my dick is stuck
ちんちん刺さってるとこ見て
Look.
ほ ら
Naughty, right?
エッチでしょ?
Please punch harder.
もっと思いっきりパンパンきなよ
Did you have a penis?
ちんちんちゃったの?
Hold this with the opposite hair.
反対の毛でこれを持って
Show me your naughty face.
いっぱいエッチな顔見せて
I'm getting excited by the extremely naughty movements.
すんごいエッチな動きにきんちゃう
That makes my dick feel so good.
それでちんちんいっぱい気持ちよくして
This is the deepest one, right?
これ一番奥当たるでしょ?
Do you like Oku Tireken?
奥疲れんの好き?
He's such a pervert
すんごい変態なんだ
death.
し
Kuru-chan is stuck in the deepest part.
く るちゃん一番奥まで刺さってる
It's cute, your face has a big dick in it.
可愛いよ、すごくちんちん入ってる顔
When I get as deep as I can.
思 いっきり奥いっぱいついたら
Come on, it's a bottle.
くる、びんびんだよ
Did you go with a thick penis?
太いちんちんでいっちゃった?
I'm being really confused, a lot.
すんごいおかされてるよ、いっぱい
Kuru-chan is more deep inside.
くるちゃんもっと奥いっぱい
It's puffy
パンパンついてる
Yo.
よ
Beautiful bread.
き れいなパンパン
This is my pussy, Kuru-chan.
このまんこだ、くるちゃん
That's amazing Manjiruta.
すんげーまんじるたって
Can I have more?
もっといっぱいついていい?
Ugh
うぅ
Uuuuuuu
ぅ ぅぅぅ
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu up
う ぅぅぅぅぅ うぅぅぅぅ うぅぅぅぅ う ぅぅぅぅ おまん
From here
こ から
Do you see it dripping?
垂 れてきてるの分かる?
Come, come.
おいで、くる
Hey, it's Kuru-chan.
おい、くるちゃんのさ
My pussy was soaked.
おまんこのびしゃびしゃになっちゃった
Please clean it with your mouth.
口できれいにしてもらえ
Add just enough to cover the roots.
根元につくぐらい加えて
Muki-chan.
む きちゃん
How was it shooting this for the first time today?
今日初めてこれ撮ってどうだった?
It was fun.
楽しかったです
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was really, really cute.
ほんとめちゃくちゃ可愛かったぞ
You were nervous today.
緊張してたね、今日ね
Hide again this time.
また今度隠れてさ
I want to take time.
時間取りたいね
good?
いい?
Promise me.
約束ね
Next, welcome back.
次、おかえりさ
Thank you.
ありがとね